Tari Shapiro

Pharmacist - Makefield Town Pharmacy

Pennsauken, NJ - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Tari-Shapiro/8b0e0c60012102eb

Experienced Pharmacist in Sterile Compounding, Speciality Pharmacy, and Supervision of technicians. Excellent

organizational and time management skills allow for fluid movement into new positions. Patient oriented with exceptional

counseling and quality patient care. Currently licensed in Pennsylvania and NJ license is pending.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Pharmacist

Makefield Town Pharmacy - Morrisville, PA - August 2015 to Present

Part-time Community Pharmacist position.

Extensive patient counseling and medication recommendation

Continual contact with staff of local physician's offices and staff for patient therapy management.

Staff Pharmacist

Careplus Pharmacy - Philadelphia, PA - March 2012 to October 2015

Checking Pharmacist for HIV, Transplant, Hepatitis C *Opened and closed the store *Managed inventory and handled customer questions *Promoted to Oncology Department handling Celgene products *Used time management and organizational skills, to worked the department to run more fluidly.

Recorded and maintained paperwork for REMS programs *Counseled patients and determined if ADE reports were taken and reported *Followed up on ADE reports and the outcome.

Staff Pharmacist PT

Temple Hospital - Philadelphia, PA - April 2010 to January 2012

Great opportunity to learn Oncology pharmacy.

Interpreted and entered physician generated orders.

Orders were checked for accuracy based on dosage and patient parameters.

Reviewed and approved MRI and CAT scan orders *Maintained Pyxis Stations *Prepared Chemotherapy in a sterile ISO 7 Environment.

Ordered and maintained inventory.

Pharmacist Staff Pharmacist/Supervisor

Central Admixture Pharmacy Services - Philadelphia, PA - March 2007 to January 2012

Interpreted and entered physician generated custom TPN and Cardioplegia orders.

Compounded orders using Baxa EM2400 Pumps • Oversee and supervise technicians during compounding to ensure aseptic technique and SOPs were followed *Interface with hospital pharmacies when orders needed further evaluation *Oversee and troubleshoot any problems that arose within the pharmacy, warehouse or delivery

process.

Pharmacist

Towne Pharmacy - Philadelphia, PA - January 1998 to January 2007

Philadelphia, NJ

Performed all standard duties required as a pharmacist *Compounded specialized prescriptions for local Dermatologists, Children's Hospital, and Physical Therapy programs *Implemented new computerized CSOS system *Assimilated Medicare D program into the system Including adding and troubleshooting all software programs *Had direct contact with insurance companies to facilitate the insureds' usage of the program *Conducted meetings at local community centers to guide Seniors and answer questions able the new Medicare

D program.

EDUCATION

Pharmacy

University of the Sciences in Philadelphia - Philadelphia, PA

CERTIFICATIONS

Pharmacist

September 2016

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Skill Highlights

Strong background in Sterile Compounding Proficient in Microsoft Office
Excellent patient interaction and counseling skills Proficient in Excel
Knowledge of USP 797 and 795 Aseptic Guidelines Excellent skills in staff motivation/teamwork
Accomplished Supervisory skills MTM Certification pending training completion